Noel Yuson

Product Designer

Las Vegas, NV

702-292-6106 | ncmyuson@gmail.com LinkedIn | GitHub

SUMMARY

I am a Product Designer proficient in prototyping, conducting usability tests, sketching, wireframing, as well as using UX/UI applications such as Figma and Adobe XD. I have 6 months of experience in UI/UX design and am continuously learning, which allowed me to develop my prototyping, wireframing, and designing skills. I also have a strong background in Photography, as well as interest in Graphic Design and Filmmaking.

SKILLS

Skills: Wireframing, Prototyping, Sketching, Usability Testing, Conducting Surveys/Interviews

Tools: Figma, Adobe XD, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Notion, Maze

PROJECTS

Tootle (Bus App) | Prototype

- Conducted market analysis to determine common user pain points using their public transit mobile app via multiple interviews and surveys.
- Prototyped an application design that addresses the shortcomings of similar apps and follows a minimalist principle to focus on key functionality that the users demand.
- Tech: Figma, Illustrator, Photoshop, Notion.

EXPERIENCE

Sales Associate

CVS Health | New York, NY

June 2021 - August 2021

- Assisted over 30 customers daily to address their needs and questions, and provided them a satisfactory experience.
- Adapted to working in various environments such as Pharmacy, Retail, Delivery, and Packaging departments
- Maintained working relationships with existing clients to ensure exceptional service and identification of potential new sales opportunities.

Sales Associate

Kroger | Las Vegas, NV

October 2018 - June 2021

- Trained multiple new hires to ensure that they conform to the guidance and rules in a clear fashion.
- Collaborated with diverse departments to understand the roles in an in-depth level and to be able to effectively communicate with them.
- Assessed current customer needs and followed a defined selling process.

EDUCATION

Product Design, Bootcamp

March 2022

Thinkful

- Completing a six month bootcamp program highlighting UI/UX principles such as prototyping, wireframing, sketching, usability testing, delivering product designs, as well as creating conceptual ideas.
- Designing project products using Figma, Illustrator, and Photoshop such as the Bus App which allowed users to navigate their commute through a public transit system

Bachelor's, Marketing 2018-2019